Anthony Badila

3D Animator - Graphic Designer - Front End Software Dev

Portfolio | Github | Linkedin | Email

I'm a 20-year-old graphic designer and software developer based in Atlanta, GA. My journey started at age 7, learning Photoshop for homeschool projects and coding Lego robots for competitions. I excel in HTML, CSS, React, and JavaScript, with experience in Python, Java, ElephantSQL, Ejs, and various aspects of API and server coding.

Software Development Skills

Java, .NET, JavaScript, Python, Node.js, React, Express, Jest, RESTful API, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, HTML, CSS, GitHub, CSS

Education

DigitalCrafts / City of Refuge | Certificate in Software Engineering | Atlanta, GA

July 2023 - November 2023

 Software engineering training program covering full-stack development including, but not limited to JavaScript, including an emphasis on cutting-edge frameworks like React and server-side technologies including Node.js, Express, and PostgreSQL.

Art Institute Of Atlanta | Graphic Design | Atlanta, GA

May 2021

Software Development Portfolio

ATHF Bootstrap Demo | Deployment | Github

July 2023

Created a Bootstrap & CSS demo in the first weeks of my Digital Crafts Bootcamp

Kanrimono | Deployment | Github

November 2023

As a member of a 4-person development team building our Capstone, my responsibilities included creating the
concept and layout of the site, all of the CSS and styling, and making all of the graphics for our site using Blender,
Procreate, and Photoshop.

Professional Work Experience

Slutty Vegan ATL | Social Media Coordinator & Shift Supervisor | Atlanta, GA

Feb 2021 - August 2021

- Posting content on social media pages and managing the customer service hotline.
- Designing merchandise and creating graphics for promotions.
- Managing and supervising my team in the restaurant.
- Cooking and operating the grill, handling the fry station, preparing burgers, operating the cash register, greeting customers at the door, stocking supplies.

Truett's Grill Chick-Fil-A | Back-of-house and Front-of-house team member | Morrow, GA June 2022 - December 2022

- Preparing food, including sandwiches.
- Operating the fryer.
- Taking customer orders and serving them.
- Handling the cash register.
- Assisting with the drive-through service.
- · Keeping supplies stocked.

Vietvana Pho Noodle House | Server and Line Cook | Atlanta, GA

January 2023 - July 2023

- Serving guests.
- Operating the cash register.
- Cooking and preparing food.
- Managing the expo station involves coordinating the presentation and final preparation of dishes before they are served to guests. This can include checking the order for accuracy, garnishing dishes, and ensuring they are correctly packaged for to-go orders.